Ta-da! Shaved ice!
Welcome!
Saaka! Uncle!
Yee!
Hello everyone!
I'm Hirao Honoka, a 4th term student of Hyuhizaka46!
Today's video is about the senior 3rd term students who will perform at the Tokyo Idol Festival tomorrow, August 4, so congratulations!
I am Hirao Honoka.
I am personally indebted to you, or rather, we get along really well every day, and I would like to help you in any way I can.
I hope I can help you in any way I can today and tomorrow,
Thank you very much.
I would like to offer something to them.
When the 4th term students were performing at the newcomers' event
When the 4th term students were performing at the newcomers' event, the 3rd term students came and brought us some goodies.
I thought it would be nice if I could bring something tasty for them, too.
So I decided to bring something delicious.
Here it is!
Here's a little something.
This way is better to see.
Like this.
Jarrah!
It's shaved ice!
Thank you for watching.
There was a shaved ice unit with the four current 3rd year students and the seniors who have already graduated.
I've been a member of this group for about 6 months now, and they've been really kind to me, so I chose to be a member of the Shaved Ice Unit.
So I chose shaved ice.
I chose shaved ice.
Myself.
I'm making a video from my house.
I'm going to make my own sauce this time.
The first one is for Hinano-san.
I'm going to make avocado shaved ice.
Hinano-san and I like unusual flavors, so we often go out for shaved ice together.
We often go out to eat together.
We both love avocado flavor.
I thought I'd make avocado flavor today, which we both love.
Ta-da!
Mixing with a mixer.
Now that the avocado is in, let's continue.
Here it is!
Add 4 tablespoons of maple syrup
Add the maple syrup and mix it in.
Add 150ml of maple syrup.
A little bit of lemon.
That's it.
And we're going to mix it.
Oh my god! That's dangerous!
Scary! It's not dangerous.
Here we go.
What do you think?
Aah! Avocado!
Ta-da!
Avocado over ice.
And some mixed nuts.
Pour it over the avocado and you're done!
First, milk
150g of milk
Mix it in.
I hope you like it.
I wonder if it's this one.
This is the sign and this is today's menu.
This reminds me of the school festival!
We're waiting for the third term students.
They'll be here soon.
Welcome!
Welcome
Welcome.
Suister...
He's going to make it for me.
Another milk.
I'll get it.
Salt.
Salt
Doctor, are you here for this?
Oh my God, you...
You're welcome, doctor.
It's been a while.
Koyamamura-san, how did you make the original?
I made it.
How did you do it?
What's this?
Woooo!
You're stocking up.
Stocking?
He was stocking up.
I'll go check it out.
Here you go.
Right here.
Back, back, back.
Let's get out of here.
Let's get out.
You think he's coming?
Oh, my God.
That's great.
It's hollow.
Now you can taste it.
I know what I'm doing.
I'll put it in the middle.
Is that milk?
That's what I'm talking about.
That's a lot of food.
Soft and fluffy.
It's fluffy.
Looks so good.
That was fast.
Oh, no, it's true.
It's so fluffy!
We're looking for this diner.
Hey, Doc.
There's also a Rastodar.
Rastodar.
Wait, it says "Rastauder" right here.
Oh, J.Q. Loos.
Oh, that's super coded!
Did you really make that?
Did you really make this?
You brought it with you, didn't you?
From the shaved ice shop.
No, no, no.
Okay, the avocado is done.
It's a little soggy.
But it's really good, in case you were wondering. Drink it.
What are you going to do? No problem!
Can I drink with you?
Bon appétit, Hirao-san!
I'm so happy. I want to drink at a restaurant.
I'd rather drink at a restaurant.
The avocado is so sweet!
I'm impressed. It's delicious.
This is amazing.
Oh, my God.
I can't wait to taste it.
It's good. It's good.
First of all, it's delicious.
Suavocado.
Bon appétit.
It's so good.
It's really good!
So delicious!
A huge sot crayon!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
For always being so nice to me.
And for letting me be a part of your group.
I appreciate that.
Oh, my God.
You're one of us.
Hearing that, Mikuni-san's feeling is
I'm one of you.
Friends!
If you like, think of me as the leader of the shaved ice club.
I'm glad
I'll take that as a compliment.
I'll do my best.
Mr. Representative Director.
Thank you, Mr. Representative Director.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thank you very much.
Please eat.
Insert
insert shot
Insert shot
Hey Shaky
Personality
Bon appétit!
Yay!
Three.
You love it.
I love it.
I feel like I won't choke.
Bon appétit.
It's a little spicy.
Are you okay? I'm glad.
It's absolutely delicious.
They go well together.
Sweet red bean paste and soy flour.
That's good.
Shaved ice for a surprise!
That's right.
Milk.
With Anko
Mmm.
Okay, bye.
I'll try my best to do a little something tomorrow.
That's great. That's really great.
Thank you. Does that mean you'll come back tomorrow?
That's for sure.
Well, actually...
I'll be a reporter tomorrow.
What? Is that really true?
Are you really saying that? Your interview.
I don't know which one.
When do you say "hyal"?
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
We'll do the interview tomorrow, and we'll film from behind the sleeves.
Oh, really?
Yes, really. Really?
Thank you very much.
As if you heard something.
I was just kidding.
That's great!
Thank you.
No, no, no, no. I'm glad to hear it.
Okay, I'll make you some rare cheese.
I really want some rare cheese.
I'll have some rare cheese, too.
It's the kind you love, Marie.
It's very soft and fluffy.
Rare cheese is very chewy.
It's very rich.
Luxurious!
I'm making it.
Thank you very much.
Now the next job, yes it's true, yes I'm anxious, thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much!
Thank you, Hiro, I love you!
See you tomorrow.
Good luck tomorrow!
Thank you very much.
They are so cute, like waiting kids!
What's with this picture? It's so cute!
What's with this picture?
the fluttering of the fluttering of the fluttering of the fluttering of the fluttering of the fluttering
it's so funny that you made it!
I'm sure it's really the store's side
The store side
Wait a minute, it looks delicious!
What a waste!
What's that over there?
I put honey on it.
It definitely goes well with it.
I'm glad.
It looks really good.
What's that over there?
Can I...
Have some of the alea cheese.
Thank you very much.
It looks really good.
It's amazing.
Yeah. - Yeah.
This is really...
Ours is really, really good.
It's not like a YouTube channel.
We can put it out, we can put it out, we can put it out, we can really put it out.
Really, really, really good.
I'm so happy.
I was so excited.
No, actually...
I know you've already graduated, but...
I wanted our seniors to try it too.
No, I'm sure he'll see it.
Really?
You'll definitely watch it?
You'll definitely see it.
It's a clasp, isn't it?
Yes, I will.
Yes. - It's luxurious.
I put this on top of the other.
Thank you.
Puppies and peas.
Papri-pippi.
What is it?
It's good!
You're right.
Here you go, Mr. Harriet.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
Here you go.
All right.
I guess they're closing for the day.
Bon appétit.
Ah-ha.
I know what you mean.
This could be a big success.
I'll stand for it.
Uma-paru.
The second time I put it...
I'll stand in for it! - I'll stand in for it!
I'm so happy!
Thank you
It's so good! Thank you!
I'm glad. Let's eat later.
Let's eat. Since you're here, let's have some Hirao.
May I?
Try it.
It'll be fun.
Delicious.
I didn't think I'd get to eat shaved ice in a whole prefecture.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad.
You've made up your own mind, haven't you?
I got the call.
He said he wanted to do it through the channel for sure.
With such enthusiasm.
I've never asked an adult for a favor before.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I like you more.
I'm glad.
I have a good junior colleague.
Tiff, I look forward to working with you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm rooting for you.
I'm now in Deft Odis on the second day!
Ta-da!
How are you guys feeling now that the show is about to start?
I'm so nervous.
Do you have any key points for today's TIFF?
I'm going to play a song from the 3rd season, so I'd like to make the audience excited.
I'm also going to do some sweet and rusty songs other than the 3rd period songs.
This is the first time for me to do a whole song with 4 members, so I'm really excited about how it's going to be.
I wonder how it will turn out.
I'm looking forward to everyone's reaction.
You're not expecting it, are you?
No way. I'm sure they didn't.
I want to show the unity of the 3rd term students.
We're going to do our best.
And we'll be right behind you.
From the back.
First, front.
First in front.
Are you okay?
Last, last, last.
That's the most important thing.
Funny.
France.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
I was wondering if I could finish. No, no, no, no, no, not at all.
I'm looking forward to it.
Where are you guys going? Sode? Sodexo, I think.
I'll do my best. Thank you.
Thank you. I'll get some.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
I'll take eight.
Thank you very much.
I'll be with you for the grand finale.
Please do.
Bye-bye.
The show is about to start.
I'm already feeling very nervous.
I'll be watching from my sleeve and other places.
I'll be rooting for you.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll dance with you in secret.
I'll dance in secret.
The second time.
I'm so scared.
Kano...
Please share your enthusiasm.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm just going to try my best to be cute and show off my teacher's charm.
I'm going to do my best to bring out the full charm of the teacher.
Please do your best!
I'll be watching.
Bye bye.
LOL!
Keep up the good work.
I'm rooting for you.
Thank you.
Keep up the good work.
I'll do my best.
LOL!
Dame backup
Can you hear me?
I haven't even left yet.
I can hear Nakasaka Hall
That's a great voice!
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh...
Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh!
Ooh-oh-oh-oh
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, hurry up
Oh, man.
It's going up a little bit.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Ooh nó
Aomi
The venue is commander
Ou commando YOzogen
Omen and
Like the right side of the students.
I might have seen it.
I have seen you
You've done your job
You've done your job.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
I was so moved, I could hardly contain my voice. How was everyone?
It was fun.
It was so much fun.
Your cheers helped me a lot.
When the overture was played, everyone was cheering so loudly.
I was about to cry in my sleeve because I was the only third-year student at the overture.
I was also getting teary-eyed.
Thank you very much.
Memories for a lifetime.
Shall we go to the next one?
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you for watching!
Subscribe to our channel and click the Good button.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!